International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge 91 Records 1984.0017
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I: Administrative Records, undated, 1947-1982
  - Subseries B: Correspondence and Subject Files, undated, 1967-1982
    - Jet News, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 143)
      - Machinists Political Leadership Institute, Univ. of PA, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 161)
      - Miscellaneous administrative files, 1967-1972 (Box 6, Folder 162)
      - Millionth member Celebration, Hartford, CT, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 163)
      - National Labor Relations Board: 1-CA-7234, 1970 Aug 10 (Box 6, Folder 164)
      - National Right to Work Committee, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 165)
      - Negotiations: Seminole Lodge 971, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 166)
      - New business, 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 167)
    - New Union News, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 168)
      - Official notice for Lodge 1746 meetings, 1968-1972 (Box 6, Folder 169-171)
      - Ostro, Justin: biographical profile, undated (Box 6, Folder 172)
      - Papps, Plato (Chief Legal Counsel), 1966-1972 (Box 6, Folder 173-174)
      - Pension plan, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 175)
      - Petition for IAM representation, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 176)
      - Planning for peace time adjustment, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 177)
      - Presidential election propaganda, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 178)
      - Politics, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 179)
      - Press releases re. Appeals Court decision, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 180)
      - Ratner, Mozart (Legal Counsel): correspondence, 1966-1974 (Box 6, Folder 181-183)
      - Ratner, Mozart: Ervin Committee, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 184)
      - Ratner, Mozart: negotiation file, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 185)
      - Referendum to amend constitution, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 186)
      - Resignations, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 187)
      - Rotating shifts, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 188)
      - Rumney Arbitration, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 189)
    - Shop committee and stewards for Lodge 1746, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 190)
    - Shut-down, 1968-1971 (Box 7, Folder 191)
    - Standing Committees of Court and Common Council, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 192)
    - Stanadyne Inc., 1980 (Box 7, Folder 193)
    - Statement of George Meany, AFL & Congress, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 194)
    - Strike donations and appeals, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 195)
    - Systematic Tax Inc., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 196)
    - Thank you letters for donations, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 197)
    - United Aircraft Corporation
      - Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 198)
      - Manpower projections, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 199)
      - Retroactive pay, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 200)
      - Stockholders meetings, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 201)
      - Street closing file, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 202)
    - United Auto Workers: contracts, undated (Box 7, Folder 203)
    - United Auto Workers: company forms, undated (Box 7, Folder 204)
    - United Auto Workers: W.H. McLaughlin, Industrial Relations Administration, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 205)
    - United Auto Workers: North Haven agreement, 1966, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 206-207)
    - United Farm Workers: organizing committee, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 208)
    - Urban Coalition of Greater Hartford, 1961-1971 (Box 7, Folder 209)
    - Urban Coalition Transportation Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 7, Folder 210)
    - U.S. Court of Appeals cases: 21469, 21690, 25112, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 211)
    - Workmens Compensation Commission: Gagnonclaimant vs. UAC (HSD), 1966 (Box 7, Folder 212)
    - Zeman and Daly: legal counsel (IAM), 1966-1969 (Box 7, Folder 213)
  - Subseries C: Strike Material, circa 1960-1963
    - Arbitration hearings: Lodge 1746 and Lodge 743 vs. United Aircraft, 1960 September 20 - 28; (2 vols.) (Box 8, Folder 214-215)
    - Arbitration: post strike submission, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 216)
    - Back pay reinstatement, undated (Box 8, Folder 217)
    - Correspondence: Daly and Kowalski re. Navy, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 218)
    - Miscellaneous strike material, undated (Box 8, Folder 219)
    - Statements of strikers returning to work, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 220)
    - Vacation pay settlement, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 221)
  - Subseries D: Legal Case Files, circa 1966-1972
    - Individual cases
      - Ardenski, Theodore: internal security, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 222-223)
      - Demerchant, Winston: discharge, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 224)
      - Pegorer, Antonio: internal security, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 225)
      - Stewards discharge, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 226)
      - Wiseman, Thomas Arthur: internal security, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 227)
    - National Labor Relations Board
      - Addresses of bargaining unit, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 228)
      - 1-CA-3355 et al., 1969, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 229-230)
      - 1-CA-5681 et al., 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 231-237)
      - 1-CA-3617, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 238-239)
      - 1-CA-6475 and 1-CA-6602, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 240-241)
      - 1-CA-6492, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 242-244)
      - 1-CA-7234, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 245-248)
    - U.S. Supreme Court Case No. 816: Lodges 1746 and 743 vs. NLRB and UAC, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 249)
    - U.S. District Court for the District of Connecticut
      - C.A. 9084-9085, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 250)
      - C.A. 11,466, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 251)
      - C.A. 13,760, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 252)
    - U.S. Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit, Case No. 34, 342; 34, 379; 34, 381, undated (Box 9, Folder 253)
  - Subseries E: Boron Cases, 1969-1976
    - Administrative files
      - Boron "office file", 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 254)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 9, Folder 255-263)
      - Miscellaneous Boron papers, 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 264)
    - Agreements
      - Contract notes, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 265)
      - Drafts and working papers, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 266-270)
      - Hamilton Standard pre-1974 job rating, undated (Box 9, Folder 271)
      - Lodge 743 and Hamilton Standard, 1969-1972 (Box 9, Folder 272)
      - Lodge 743 and Hamilton Standard, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 273)
      - Other representative contracts, 1971, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 274)
    - Negotiations
      - Proposals, undated (Box 9, Folder 275)
      - 1970 (Box 9, Folder 276)
      - Composite notes, undated (Box 9, Folder 277)
      - 1972 (Box 9, Folder 278-279)
    - Cases and litigation
    - U.S. Court of Appeals for the Second Circuit: case No. 73-1148, undated (Box 9, Folder 280)
      - NLRB Case 1-CA-7182, 1970-1972; (3 folders) (Box 9, Folder 281-283)
      - NLRB Case 1-CA-8370, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 284)
      - NLRB Case 1-CB-1954, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 285)
  - Subseries F: Preference for Bargaining Survey, 1974
    - Correspondence, 1974 July 29 (Box 11, Folder 286)
    - Detail reports and summary analysis
      - Lodge 700, 1974 June (Box 11, Folder 287-289)
      - Lodge 1747A, 1974 June (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - Subseries G: Lou Kiefer Files, circa 1960-1982
    - Correspondence
      - AFL-CIO, 1971, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 291)
      - AFL-CIO, COPE, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 292)
      - Canel Lodge 700, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 293)
      - Civic organizations, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 294)
      - Colt Industries, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 295)
      - Congressional correspondence, 1977, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 296)
      - Connecticut State Labor Council, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 297)
      - District 91, 1976-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 298)
      - IAMAW, 1968-1981 (Box 12, Folder 299-307)
      - Lodge 1746, 1957, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 308)
      - Miscellaneous, 1960-1980 (Box 12, Folder 309)
      - Other locals, 1960-1980 (Box 12, Folder 310)
      - Ratner, Mozart, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 311)
      - State of Connecticut, 1971, 1977, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 312)
      - Steward letter, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 313)
      - TNE letter, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 314)
      - University of Connecticut, 1977, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 315)
    - Administrative Files
      - Accessory Controls Equipment Co., 1977 June 27 (Box 12, Folder 316)
      - Case No's 1-CB-2710, 2711, 2721, 2722 and non-member listing, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 317)
      - Cartoon drafts, undated (Box 12, Folder 318)
      - Connecticut Environmental Caucus, 1977 August 2 (Box 12, Folder 319)
      - Connecticut General Life Insurance Company, undated (Box 12, Folder 320)
      - Dropouts, 1978, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 321-322)
      - Environmental watch, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 323)
      - Fifty leading exporters, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 324)
      - Flyers, 1977-1983 (Box 12, Folder 325)
      - Greater Hartford Labor Council, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 326)
      - Grievance: Laks, Joel, improper, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 327)
      - Group Insurance benefits, 1968-1982 (Box 12, Folder 328)
      - Health, Welfare and Pension Programs, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 329)
      - Interviews on questions of military spending and contracts affecting employment, undated (Box 12, Folder 330)
      - Laid-off member letter, undated (Box 12, Folder 331)
      - Lay-off Alert Program, undated (Box 12, Folder 332)
      - Lay off: "An important reminder from your union", undated (Box 12, Folder 333)
      - Local Lodge weighted average hourly earnings, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 334)
      - Magazine project, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 335)
      - Membership configurations, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 336)
      - Negotiations wage opener, 1977, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 337-339)
      - Nelsonville story, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 340)
      - Newsletter paste ups and cartoons, ca. 1980s (Box 12, Folder 341)
      - Pratt and Whitney: ECI commendations, 1971 April 16 (Box 12, Folder 342)
      - Pratt and Whitney: Internal correspondence, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 343)
      - Skills lost to lay-off, 1982 January 27 (Box 12, Folder 344)
      - Sullivan: notes, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 345)
      - Surveys, 1977-1981 (Box 12, Folder 346)
      - Swanson, Norman Research Subcommittee, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 347)
      - Testimony: Environmental committee, undated (Box 12, Folder 348)
      - Testimony: submitted before the members of plant closings and relocation committee, 1982 February 5 (Box 12, Folder 349)
      - 30 and out, 1980s (Box 12, Folder 350)
      - TNE: Job erosion at UTC, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 351)
      - TNE: "Co-production", 1978 (Box 12, Folder 352)
      - TNE: Tax Reform, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 353)
      - United Technologies Corporation: master plan, undated (Box 12, Folder 354)
      - United Technologies reprints: OP-ED, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 355)
      - Wolf, Herman: re. Connecticut General Life Insurance Company, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 356)
  - Subseries H: Dave Cooper Files, 1975-1980
    - General files, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 357-365)
    - Advanced Industrial Management Seminar, ca. 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 366)
    - Arbitrations, undated, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 367-368)
    - Connecticut State Labor Council minutes, 19?? (Box 13, Folder 369)
    - Contract negotiations, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 370)
    - Correspondence, ca. 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 371)
    - C.P.I. formula for negotiations, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 372)
    - Dental plan notes, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 373)
    - Employee benefits, 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 374-375)
    - Employee "memorandums", 1978 (Box 13, Folder 376)
    - Executive summary: Japanese management, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 377)
    - Financial reports, 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 378)
    - Greater Hartford Labor Council, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 379)
    - Grievances: appeals, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 380)
    - Grievances: employee statements, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 381)
    - Grievances: fact sheets, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 382-383)
    - IAMAW: Civil Rights Conference, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 384)
    - IAMAW: Machinery and Manufacturing Conference, 1908 (Box 13, Folder 385)
    - Management's rights, undated (Box 13, Folder 386)
    - Pratt and Whitney: correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 387)
    - Pratt and Whitney: occupational groups, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 388)
    - United Way, 1976-1980 (Box 13, Folder 389)
- Series II: Agreements and Negotiations, circa 1950-1983
  - Negotiations
    - 1965-1971 (Box 14, Folder 390-396)
    - 1974 (Box 14, Folder 397-414)
    - 1977-1980 (Box 14, Folder 415-416)
  - Agreements
    - Lodge 700: Middletown, 1966, 1977, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 417-419)
    - Lodge 707: North Haven, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 420)
    - Lodge 743: Windsor Locks, 1950-1983 (Box 15, Folder 421-428)
    - Lodge 1746 East Hartford, 1966-1982 (Box 15, Folder 429-434)
    - Lodge 1746A: Southington, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 435)
    - All Lodges: "Articles", 1982 (Box 15, Folder 436)
  - Printed Contracts
    - Lodge 700, 1971, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 437)
    - Lodge 707, 1975, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 438)
    - Lodge 743, 1966-1978 (Box 16, Folder 439)
    - Lodge 1746, 1966-1977 (Box 16, Folder 440-441)
    - Lodge 1746A, 1971, 1974, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 442)
- Series III: Financial Records, circa 1955-1973
  - Correspondence
    - 1954-1963 (Box 17, Folder 443-444)
    - Insurance, 1954-1960 (Box 17, Folder 445)
    - Workers injury cooperative survey, 1966, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 446)
  - Financial reports
    - Annual financial report, 1960-1961, 1969-1973 (Box 17, Folder 447-449)
    - Audit reports, 1963-1970 (Box 17, Folder 450)
    - Employer contribution returns, 1964-1969 (Box 17, Folder 451)
    - Federal income tax returns, 1964-1969 (Box 17, Folder 452)
    - Monthly statements, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 453)
    - Property tax: East Hartford, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 454)
    - Social Security deductions, 1954-1959 (Box 17, Folder 455)
  - Volumes
    - Treasures Cash book, 1954-1960; (3 volumes)
    - Cash book, 1967-1969
    - Ledgers, 1954-1955; (2 volumes)
    - Payroll book, 1955-1957
    - "Financial Secretary's Reference Manual", 1955
- Series VI: Civil Case 9084-9085: United States Superior Court, District of Connecticut, undated, 1962-1969
  - Subseries A: Pleadings and Indexes, undated, 1962-1967
    - Cross index of volumes, undated (Box 21, Folder 519)
    - Plaintiffs exhibits index, undated (Box 21, Folder 520-521)
    - Index of transcript pages wherein the plaintiff's exhibits are discussed, undated (Box 21, Folder 522)
    - Defendants exhibits index, undated (Box 21, Folder 523)
    - Index of transcript pages where defendants exhibits are discussed, undated (Box 21, Folder 524)
    - List of documents on which the plaintiffs propose to rely in support of their affirmative case, 1966 January 10 (Box 21, Folder 525-526)
    - Consolidated Cases pleadings index, 1962-1964 (Box 21, Folder 527)
      - 9084: Pleadings, vol. 1, 1962-1964 (Box 21, Folder 528)
      - 9084-9085: Pleadings, vol. 11, 1962 January - November (Box 21, Folder 529)
      - 9084-9085: Pleadings, vol. 111, 1963 July - December (Box 21, Folder 530)
      - 9084-9085: Pleadings, vol. 111A, special volume, 1963 November (Box 21, Folder 531)
      - 9084-9085: Pleadings, vol. IV, 1963 December - 1964 January (Box 21, Folder 532)
      - 9084-9085: Pleadings, vol. V, 1964 February - April (Box 21, Folder 533)
      - 9084-9085: Pleadings, vol. VI, 1964 May - July (Box 21, Folder 534)
      - 9084-9085: Pleadings, vol. VIII, 1964 November - 1965 October (Box 21, Folder 535)
      - 9084-9085: Pleadings, vol. VIII, 1965 November - 1966 May (Box 22, Folder 536)
      - 9084-9085: Pleadings, vol. IX, 1966 May - 1967 November (Box 22, Folder 537)
  - Subseries B: Briefs and Memoranda, 1962-1969
    - Memorandum of decisions on motion for more definitive statement, 1962 March 26 (Box 22, Folder 538)
    - Motion for reconsideration of decision and ruling of defendant's motion for a more definitive statement and to strike, 1962 April 15 (Box 22, Folder 539)
    - Notice to take deposition, 1962 June 14 (Box 22, Folder 540)
    - Memorandum in support of defendant's objections to plaintiff's interrogatories, 1962 November 29 (Box 22, Folder 541)
    - Opposition of plaintiff to motion of defendant to suspend reply to plaintiff's reply to defendant's objections to interrogatories, 1962 December 7 (Box 22, Folder 542)
    - Ruling on defendant's motion to suspend interrogatories and defendant's objection to interrogatories, 1963 January 8 (Box 22, Folder 543)
    - Ruling on defendant's motion for reconsideration of court's ruling of January 8, 1963 and plaintiff's motion to strike, 1963 March 13 (Box 22, Folder 544)
    - Defendant's claim in set off, 1963 April 9 (Box 22, Folder 545)
    - Motion of NLRB for leave to intervene, 1963 July 10 (Box 22, Folder 546)
    - Ruling on the plaintiff's amended motion for and order pursuant to rule 34 of Federal civil procedure, 1963 October 31 (Box 22, Folder 547)
    - Motion to strike defendant's interrogatories, 1963 November 20 (Box 22, Folder 548)
    - Memorandum in support of motion to strike, 1963 November 20 (Box 22, Folder 549)
    - Motion to permit a lawyer represent defendant, 1963 November 27 (Box 22, Folder 550)
    - Substituted request for admission of genuineness of documents, 1964 April 22 (Box 22, Folder 551)
    - Ruling on the defendant's objection to plaintiff's interrogatories, 1964 April 22 (Box 22, Folder 552)
    - Ruling on the defendant's motion to vacate the notices to take depositions and to quash request for production of documents, 1964 April 22 (Box 22, Folder 553)
    - Ruling on plaintiff's motion to take deposition and defendant's motion for orders under rules (37b) and 12F striding affidavits, 1964 April 24 (Box 22, Folder 554)
    - Consolidate amended complaint, 1964 November 27 (Box 22, Folder 555)
    - Ruling on defendant's motion to strike consolidated amended complaint, 1965 April 1 (Box 22, Folder 556)
    - Defendant's motion to dismiss portions of the complaint for lack of jurisdiction, 1965 April 1 (Box 22, Folder 557)
    - Motion for more definite statement, 1965 April 1 (Box 22, Folder 558)
    - Reply of plaintiff's to defendant's motion to dismiss portions of the complaint for lack of jurisdiction, 1965 April 1 (Box 22, Folder 559)
    - Plaintiff's reply to motion for more definitive statement, 1965 June 6 (Box 22, Folder 560)
    - Ruling on defendant's motion to dismiss portions of the complaint, 1965 July 16 (Box 22, Folder 561)
    - Motion to amend consolidated amended complaint, 1965 August 23 (Box 22, Folder 562)
    - Plaintiff's more definitive statement, 1965 August 23 (Box 23, Folder 563)
    - More definitive statement
      - Count 1: Schedule 1, 1965 August 23; (4 vols.)
    - Count 1: Schedule 2A, 1965 August 23; (2 vols.)
    - Count 1: Schedule 2B, 1965 August 23; (2 vols.)
    - Count 111: Schedule 3, 1965 August 23 (Box 23, Folder 564)
    - Count 111: Schedule 4A, 1965 August 23 (Box 23, Folder 565)
    - Count 111: Schedule 4B, 1965 August 23 (Box 23, Folder 566)
    - Ruling on Plaintiff's motion to appeal consolidated amended complaint, 1965 October 29 (Box 23, Folder 567)
    - Defendant's answer to a consolidated amended complaint, 1965 November 12 (Box 23, Folder 568)
    - Plaintiff's statement of items to be considered at pre-trial conference, 1965 December 2 (Box 24, Folder 569)
    - Pre-trial order, 1965 December 2 (Box 24, Folder 570)
    - Exhibits to plaintiff's estimate of individual damages, 1966 January 28 (Box 24, Folder 571)
    - List of documents on which the plaintiffs propose to rely in support of their case, 1966 January 10 (Box 24, Folder 572)
    - Defendant's response to plaintiff's "list of documents", 1966 January 28 (Box 24, Folder 573)
    - Plaintiff's memorandum of law on the issue to be litigated, 1966 February 25 (Box 24, Folder 574)
    - Memorandum for plaintiff in opposition to defendants motion to dismiss the complaint, 1966 April 20 (Box 24, Folder 575)
    - Ruling on defendants motion to dismiss complaint and modification of pre-trial order, 1966 May 11 (Box 24, Folder 576)
    - Memorandum in support of motion for partial judgment on the pleadings, 1966 May 15 (Box 24, Folder 577)
    - Reply of plaintiffs to defendant's memorandum on plaintiff's motion for partial judgment as to liability only, etc., 1966 May 18 (Box 24, Folder 578)
    - Defendant's memorandum of law on the issues to be litigated, 1966 July 15 (Box 24, Folder 579)
    - List of documents upon which the defendants rely, 1967 February 6 (Box 24, Folder 580)
    - Plaintiff's statement of issues to be adjudicated, 1967 July 28 (Box 24, Folder 581)
    - Brief for plaintiff, Vol. 1: Statement of the case, 1968 February 1 (Box 24, Folder 582)
    - Brief for plaintiff, Vol. 2: Argument, 1968 February 1 (Box 24, Folder 583)
    - Brief for the plaintiffs, Vol. 3: Appendices, 1968 February 1 (Box 24, Folder 584)
    - Plaintiffs' proposed findings of fact and conclusions of law, 1968 February 12 (Box 24, Folder 585)
    - Defendants' brief and proposed finding of fact, 1968 May 6 (Box 24, Folder 586)
    - Reply brief for plaintiffs, 1969 June 3 (Box 24, Folder 587)
    - Memorandum of decision, 1969 March 19 (Box 24, Folder 588)
  - Subseries C: Hearings, 1962-1966
    - 1962 (Box 25, Folder 589-591)
    - 1963 (Box 25, Folder 592-597)
    - 1964 (Box 25, Folder 598-601)
    - 1965 (Box 25, Folder 602-605)
    - 1966 (Box 25, Folder 606)
    - Partial judgment on liability, 1966 May 23 (Box 25, Folder 607)
  - Subseries D: Interrogatories, undated, 1962-1963
    - 2nd series, undated (Box 25, Folder 608)
    - 1st series, 1961 October 21 (Box 25, Folder 609)
    - 2nd, 3rd, and 4th series, 1963 June 10; (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 610)
    - 6th series, 1963 December 8 (Box 25, Folder 611)
    - 50, undated (Box 25, Folder 612)
  - Subseries E: Depositions, 1962-1968
    - 1962-1964
      - Burke, Martin F., 1962 June 19 (Box 25, Folder 613)
      - 1963 April 23
      - Diefendenen, William E., 1963 October 12 (Box 25, Folder 614)
      - Lee, Harold S., 1963 December 9 (Box 25, Folder 615)
      - Morse, Nathaniel, 1962 June 20 (Box 25, Folder 616)
      - Morse, Nathaniel, 1964 February 10 (Box 25, Folder 617)
      - Pinchera, Anthony P., 1963 August 26 (Box 25, Folder 618)
      - Tierney, Raymond J., 1963 October 28 (Box 25, Folder 619)
      - Treadwell, Robert C., 1964 May 8 (Box 25, Folder 620)
      - Vandervoort, James E., 1963 October 24 (Box 25, Folder 621)
      - 1964 Feb 10
    - Certified transcript pages from 7084-9085, 1968 June - July (Box 25, Folder 622)
    - Witness testimony, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 623)
  - Subseries F: Transcripts, 1967
    - Day 1- day 16, pp. 1-3359, 1967 February 21 - March 31 (Box 26, Folder 624-639)
    - Day 17-day 32, pp. 3360-6835, 1967 April 4 - May 10 (Box 27, Folder 640-657)
    - Day 33- day 50, pp. 6835-9980, 1967 February 21 - July 7 (Box 28, Folder 658-675)
  - Subseries G: Exhibits, undated
    - Plaintiffs' exhibits
      - P1-P21c (Box 29, Folder 676-710)
      - P21d-P37 (Box 30, Folder 711-734)
      - P22, (9 volumes) (Box 30a)
      - P38-P95 (Box 31, Folder 735-788)
      - P96-P179 (Box 32, Folder 789-872)
      - P180-P322 (Box 33, Folder 873-1022)
      - P287, 288, 304, (3 vols.) (Box 33a)
      - P323-P371 (Box 34, Folder 1023-1070)
    - Defendants' exhibits
      - D1-D74 (Box 35, Folder 1071-1177)
      - D75-D85a (Box 36, Folder 1178-1195)
  - Subseries H: Attorney's Working Papers, 1944-1968
    - Correspondence, circa 1960-1966 (Box 37, Folder 1196-1198)
    - Post-strike arbitration, IAM vs. UAW, 1960 (Box 37, Folder 1199)
    - Complaints and Pleadings, 1961-1966 (Box 37, Folder 1200)
    - Consolidated, amended complaint, 1960-1965 (Box 37, Folder 1201)
    - Interrogatories and admission of facts, 1962-1964 (Box 37, Folder 1202-1203)
    - Lists of employees not rehired after strike, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 1204)
    - Federal District Court suit, 1746, 746, 1960-1964 (Box 37, Folder 1205)
    - Defendant's counterclaim, 1963 May 27 (Box 38, Folder 1206)
    - NLRB violations, 1746, 743, 1963-1964 (Box 38, Folder 1207)